{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Davis_(Kansas_politician)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Paul Davis (Kansas politician)",
    "human_readable": "The label of Paul Davis (Kansas politician) is Paul Davis (Kansas politician).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9645153284072876,
            "question": "Is Paul Davis a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8899580240249634,
            "question": "Who is Paul Davis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8003587126731873,
            "question": "What political position did Paul Davis hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7798208594322205,
            "question": "What is Paul Davis known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7726510167121887,
            "question": "Which state is Paul Davis associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7576258778572083,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Paul Davis's political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6894432306289673,
            "question": "Where did Paul Davis work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6798964142799377,
            "question": "What is Paul Davis's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6584907174110413,
            "question": "Does Paul Davis have a specific title or role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060073375701904,
            "question": "Is there anything else notable about Paul Davis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Paul Davis (Kansas politician) is Paul Davis (Kansas politician).",
            "html": "dbpedia_3753_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Paul Davis have a specific title or role?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3753_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Paul Davis's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3753_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Paul Davis work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3753_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_173.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3753_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple \"The label of Paul Davis (Kansas politician) is Paul Davis (Kansas politician)\".\n\nThe documents mention various times that a person named Paul Davis is being referred to, and it is consistently clear that this person is the same individual, a Kansas politician."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context confirms that Paul Davis is a Kansas politician, specifically mentioned as the Democratic nominee for governor in 2014 and the House Minority Leader. Therefore, the statement \"the label of Paul Davis (Kansas politician) is Paul Davis (Kansas politician)\" is accurate based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}